

Moulvibazar City, Sylhet

PROFILE

I have developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake. As a graduate I have supervisory and information technology related experience across several industries. 14 years of provisional training, promoting lateral thinking and quick solution. Proficient in computer operation and professional communication. Comfortable learning new skills and applying existing experience to new task. Emphasis on professional collaboration and problem solving on time with excellence.

CONTACT

DOB – 05/03/1981 Phone: +8801700507524 Email: brissyed@gmail.com

GITHUB:

https://aithub.com/muhitrahman

MUHIT RAHMAN

CURRENT DEVELOPMENT

- Completed Udemy MySQL database bootcamp
- Completed LCO web development Django bootcamp
- Finishing complete Android developer and Node.js bootcamp
- Studying HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Python, Database and Mobile Apps via online tutorials and side projects
- Connected with StackOverflow and another community
- Comfortable with GitHub
- Currently working on my independent projects

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Debt Collector, Protik Multipurpose Co-operative_Society Moulvibazar --- April 2017 to Onward

- Customer relationship.
- Reviewing examples of credit policies that work
- Creating new plans to maximize collections success
- Using negotiations and conflict resolution for collection
- Employing clever timing strategies to get paid first

Project Contributor and Students Assistant, Intech Institute of Technology

Brisbane, Australia --- April 2015 to February 2016

- Contributed on skilling India project for Mindstorms EV3 robotics booklet
- Assist students with their study

Travel Guide, Tangalooma Island Brisbane, Australia --- January 2014 to March 2015

 Sales and collect customer tickets and assure their safety way to the cruise ship and guide them on Tangalooma Island

Assistant Manager and cook, Oporto
Brisbane, Australia --- January 2010 to February 2016

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhit-rahman-2a3636165/

YOUTUBE:

Channel under construction

HOBBIES:

Soccer Movies Customer service, clean line safety, order placement, stock control, cash handling, everyday business update on system

Pizza Chef, Cozy Fine Dinning Italiano Brisbane, Australia --- January 2010 to March 2011

- Preparation for Pizza section
- Making Pizza according to order
- Clean line

Student Service Manager, Mentors education

Moulvibazar, Sylhet --- 2008

- Handling students complain
- Customer service
- Bookkeeping student's data
- Business improvement

Contractor, Water Supply and Sanitation, PHD, Bangladesh Govt. Moulvibazar, Sylhet --- February 2003 to May 2007

Water supply and sanitation for rural area development

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2014-2016

Intech institute of Technology, Australia Advance diploma in computer system technology

 Software development, Networking, Cyber Security, Robotics

2013-2014

Canterbury Technical Institute, Australia Diploma in software development

Software development, web development

2011

Captain Cook College, Australia

Certificate 3 in information technology

2003

National University, Moulvibazar

• Bachelor's degree in social science

1999

Dhaka State College, Dhaka

Higher Secondary Certificate in Science

1996

Patanusher High School, Moulvibazar

Secondary school certificate in science

PERSONAL SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Object oriented languages (OOP)
- Windows server 2008R2 and Cisco routing
- software development methodology, Linux basics, ethical hacking, penetration, scanning, security
- VMware, GNS3, PT
- Web design and mobile apps

REFEREES

Mr. Robin

Teacher, Intech Institute of Technology Phone - +61422524728

Mr. Steve

Teacher, Canterbury Technical Institute Phone - +61433178499

Mr. Vic

Owner, Oporot, Brisbane Central Phone - 0730127822

Mr. Sam Mura

Head Chef, Cosi Ristorante Italiano, Clayfield Phone - 07 3862 2160

Thank you for your time and consideration